Thien An Tran

Date of birth: 24-03-1996

Gender: Male

Phone: +3584578725818 Email: tranthie04@gmail.com

Address: Kitarakuja 1 A 45, 00420, Helsinki, Finland

PERSONAL PROFILE

A motivated, adaptable, responsible person embarking on taking his very first steps to start his career. He hopes he can utilize all abilities and work experience in order to deliver the best results. Besides, he is devoted to working because my priority is giving everybody the best service.

EDUCATION

2011 - 2014 Tran Dai Nghia High School For The Gifted, Ho Chi

Minh City, Vietnam

Major in Physics

2017 - now Haaga-Helia University of Applied Sciences

Business and Information Technology

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2020 Portfolio Web App

Nov 2019 - Dec 2019 Trainings Management Web Project

Jun 2019 Project 10 days 100 challenges

Dec 2014 - Now Part-time job at Restaurants, Warehouses as waiters,

kitchen staff, warehouse worker

2011 - 2014 Hoa Phuong Do Campaign of Ho Chi Minh City

Raised funds for charity

SKILLS AND CERTIFICATION

Main skills JavaScript, Reactjs, MySQL, HTML5, CSS3 and basic

Nodejs, Java, Spring boot, VueJs

Other skills Mathematical skills (Basic Calculus, Descriptive

Statistics), Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint),

SPSS, Blender, 3D Printing

Language skills Vietnamese (mother- tongue)

English (academic proficiency – IELTS: 6.0)

Finnish (Finnish for beginners 2)

Chinese (Basis Oral)

Service skills Communication with patrons, teamwork with

colleagues, serving and arranging products.

Certification Hygiene passport

INTERESTS

I enjoy watching movies, eating delicacies and socializing with friends and family.

This is the end. Thank you for reading until this part and I wish you have a nice day!